Skip to Header Skip to Main Content Skip to Footer

You are currently on the United States site.

Select a location to view location-specific content and shop online.

Switch to

* [Store](https://www.razer.com/store)Store
    
    Shop
    ----
    
    * Shop PC
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Shop Console
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Shop Mobile
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Shop Lifestyle
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Purchase Program
        
        Explore
        -------

* [PC](https://www.razer.com/pc)PC
    
    Explore
    -------
    
    * Laptops & Accessories
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Docks & Hubs
            
            Explore
            -------

        * Stands & Risers
            
            Explore
            -------

        * Adapters & Chargers
            
            Explore
            -------

        * Accessories
            
            Explore
            -------

    * Desktops & Components
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Gamer Room
        
        Explore
        -------

        Product Line
        ------------

    * Mice
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Esports
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Immersive
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * MMO
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        Product Line
        ------------
        
        * Viper
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * DeathAdder
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Cobra
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Basilisk
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Naga
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Pro Click
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * Mats
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Esports
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Immersive
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        Product Line
        ------------
        
        * Strider
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Firefly
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * Keyboards
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Esports
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Immersive
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Low-Profile
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        Product Line
        ------------
        
        * Huntsman
            
            Product Line
            ------------
            
            * Razer Huntsman V3 X Tenkeyless
            
        * BlackWidow
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * DeathStalker
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Ornata
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Tartarus
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * Headsets
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Esports
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Immersive
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Multi-Platform
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        Product Line
        ------------
        
        * Kitty Headset
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * BlackShark
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Kraken
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Barracuda
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * Speakers
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Soundbar
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Speakers
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * Content Creation
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Microphones
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Webcams
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Kitty Headset
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Stream Controllers
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Lighting & Staging
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        Product Line
        ------------
        
        * Seiren
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Kiyo
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Kraken Kitty
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Stream Controller
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * Productivity
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Mice
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Mats
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Keyboards
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Audio
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Webcams
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        Product Line
        ------------
        
        * Razer Pro Click
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * Chairs
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Ergonomic
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Breathable
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Comfort
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Licensed Editions
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Haptic Gaming Cushion
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        Product Line
        ------------
        
        * Enki
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Fujin
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Iskur
            
            Product Line
            ------------
            
            * View All Iskur

    * Software
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * More Software
            
            Product Line
            ------------

* [Console](https://www.razer.com/console-gaming)Console
    
    Explore
    -------
    
    * Xbox
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Controllers
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Controllers with Charging Stand
            
            Product Line
            ------------
            
            * [Razer Wireless Controller & Quick Charging Stand Razer Limited Edition](https://www.razer.com/console-controllers/razer-xbox-controller-and-charging-stand)
            * [Razer Sonic the Hedgehog Razer Wireless Controller & Quick Charging Stand](https://www.razer.com/console-controllers/sonic-xbox-controller-and-charging-stand)
            
        * Charging Stands
            
            Product Line
            ------------
            
            * [Razer Universal Quick Charging Stand - Forza Horizon 5 Limited Edition](https://www.razer.com/console-accessories/razer-universal-quick-charging-stand-for-xbox-forza-horizon-5)
            * [Razer Universal Quick Charging Stand - Xbox 20th Anniversary Limited Edition](https://www.razer.com/console-accessories/razer-universal-quick-charging-stand-for-xbox-20-anniversary)
            
        * Headsets
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Earbuds
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * PlayStation
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Controllers
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Headsets
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Earbuds
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Charging Stands
            
            Product Line
            ------------

* [Mobile](https://www.razer.com/mobile)Mobile
    
    Explore
    -------
    
    * Controllers
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Meta Quest
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * [Razer Adjustable Head Strap System Authorized for Meta Quest 2 and 3](https://www.razer.com/console-gaming/adjustable-head-strap-and-facial-interface-for-meta-quest-3)
        
    * Headphones
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Earbuds
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Cases
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Accessories
        
        Explore
        -------

* [Lifestyle](https://www.razer.com/lifestyle)Lifestyle
    
    Explore
    -------
    
    * Chairs
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Ergonomic
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Breathable
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Comfort
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Licensed Editions
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Haptic Gaming Cushion
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        Product Line
        ------------
        
        * Enki
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Fujin
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Iskur
            
            Product Line
            ------------
            
            * View All Iskur

    * Collabs
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Razer | Hello Kitty and Friends
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Razer | Fortnite
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Razer | PUBG: BATTLEGROUNDS
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * Apparel
        
        Explore
        -------
        
        * Xanthus
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Razer | Evisu
            
            Product Line
            ------------
            
            * [Razer | Evisu Daicock Print with Embroidery Carrot-Fit Denim Jeans](https://www.razer.com/apparel-bottoms/evisu-razer-daicock-print-with-embroidery-carrot-fit-jeans)
            
        * Instinct
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Genesis
            
            Product Line
            ------------

        * Unleashed
            
            Product Line
            ------------

    * Bags
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Accessories
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Sneki Snek
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Mac
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Gamer Room
        
        Explore
        -------

        Product Line
        ------------

* [Gold](https://gold.razer.com/us/en)Gold
    
    Explore
    -------
    
    * Razer Gold Online Store
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Game Recharge
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Payment Methods
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Rewards
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Be A Business Partner
        
        Explore
        -------

* [Community](https://www.razer.com/community)Community
    
    Explore
    -------
    
    * Sustainability
        
        Explore
        -------

    * Downloads
        
        Explore
        -------

* [Support](https://mysupport.razer.com/)Support
    
    Product Line
    ------------

Search razer.com

Begin typing to search, use arrow keys to navigate, Enter to select

0

0 more item in your cart0 more items in your cart[checkout](https://www.razer.com/cart)

Your Cart is empty.

From Sep 28 to Oct 5 2024, earn up to 150K bonus Razer Silver with your purchases as a RazerStore Rewards member. [Join Now For Free \>](https://www.razer.com/razercon)

RAZER CUSTOMER PRIVACY POLICY
=============================

Last Modified: 27 Oct 2023

1. **1\. Privacy Policy**  
    Razer Inc. and its affiliates ("Razer, we/us/our") are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers and users ("you/your") and the Personal Information you have entrusted to us. It is important for you to understand what **Personal Information** we will collect, how we will use it, and who may access it.  
      
    **Personal Information** means information about an identifiable individual. It includes information that you have provided to us or was collected by us from other sources. It may include details such as your name and address, age and gender, personal financial records, identification numbers including your Social Insurance Number and personal references, to the extent permitted by local laws.  
      
    This Privacy Policy governs your use as a visitor and/or user to [www.razer.com](https://www.razer.com/) and/ or other websites managed by Razer that reference the Privacy Policy (the "Razer Sites"). Please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By using, accessing and/or visiting the Razer Sites, you accept and agree to the Privacy Policy. If you do not accept and agree to the Privacy Policy, you should immediately stop using, accessing, and/or visiting the Razer Sites.  
      
    Children’s Privacy. Razer’s services are intended for general audiences and not for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 and if we become aware of such collection, we will take reasonable steps to delete any such information as soon as practicable.  
      
    If you are an existing customer of ours, further details about how we use your Personal Information is set out in your customer contract with us. Further notices highlighting certain uses we wish to make of your Personal Information together with the ability to opt in or out of selected uses may also be provided when we collect Personal Information from you.  
      
    Our websites may contain links to other third party websites. If you follow a link to any of those third party websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies or processing of your Personal Information. Please check these policies before you submit any Personal Information to such third party websites.  
      
    This Privacy Policy is intended to explain our privacy practices and covers the following areas:  
      
    (a) What Personal Information about you we may collect.  
      
    (b) How we may use your Personal Information.  
      
    (c) Who we may share your Personal Information with.  
      
    (d) How we protect your Personal Information.  
      
    (e) Contacting us & your rights to prevent marketing and to access and update your Personal Information.  
      
    (f) Our Cookies Policy.  
      
    (g) How changes to this Privacy Policy and the Cookies Policy will be made.  

2. **2\. Information We May Collect About You**  
    We will collect and process all or some of the following Personal Information about you:  
      
    (a) **Information you provide to us**. Personal Information that you provide to us, such as when using the contact form on our website, including your name, email address, and other contact details;  
      
    (b) **Our correspondence**. if you contact us, we will typically keep a record of that correspondence;  
      
    (c) **Information about how you use our products and services** such as information about the amount of time you use our products/services for the pages you visit, and other information about your activities while using our hardware or software or while logged into your Razer ID account. We collect this in order to develop our products and services, and to understand what your usage patterns and preferences are so that our marketing is relevant to you;  
      
    (d) **Survey information** we may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes. In such circumstances we shall collect the information provided in the completed survey;  
      
    (e) **Promotions** we may request Personal Information to administer your participation in contests, sweepstakes or other promotions that we organize;  
      
    (f) **Device Information** such as information about your operating system, browser, software applications, IP address, geolocation, security status and other device information in order to improve your experience, to protect against fraud and manage risk;  
      
    (g) **Marketing preference information** details of your marketing preferences (e.g. communication preferences) and information relevant to selecting appropriate products and services to offer you;  
      
    (h) **Website and communication usage** details of your visits to the websites and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies including, but not limited to, your IP address and domain name, your browser version and operating system, traffic data, location data, web logs, posts on the Razer Insider forum, other communication data, and the resources that you access;  
      
    (i) **Activities on Social Networking Sites (SNS)** if you choose to participate (for example, by "liking" Razer's profile on Facebook or Twitter, posting a message, or answering a poll), we will have access to the information you divulge which may include Personal Information, depending on your SNS privacy settings.  
      
    (j) **Tokens from Third Party Websites.** If you install Razer Nexus on your device and choose to link Razer Nexus to your YouTube account, Razer Nexus will access your Google account to obtain a token generated by Google dynamically. This token is a unique identifier we use for the purpose of validating and retrieving the streaming endpoint, so that Razer Nexus can match and transmit your stream to the correct YouTube channel. No personally identifiable data is obtained or stored by Razer in this process, nor is any transferred to any third party.Your video stream will be passed through to YouTube.  

3. **3\. Uses Made of your Personal Information:**  
    In this section, we set out the purposes for which we use Personal Information that we collect via our website and, in compliance with our obligations under local laws and European law, identify the "legal grounds" on which we rely to process the information.  
      
    These "legal grounds" allow companies to process personal data only when the processing is permitted by the specific "legal grounds" set out in local laws or European law, as applicable.  
      
    **Consent:** where you have consented to our use of your information  
      
    **Contract performance:** where your information is necessary to enter into or perform our contract with you.  
      
    **Legal obligation:** where we need to use your information to comply with our legal obligations.  
      
    **Legitimate interests:** where we use your information to achieve a legitimate interest and our reasons for using it outweigh any prejudice to your data protection rights.  
      
    **Legal claims:** where your information is necessary for us to defend, prosecute or make a claim against you, us or a third party.  
    If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place. Where we are using your information because we or a third party (e.g. your employer) have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Services.  
      
    Please note that in addition to the disclosures we have identified below, we may disclose Personal Information for the purposes we explain in this notice to service providers, contractors, agents, advisors (e.g. legal, financial, business or other advisors) and affiliates of Razer that perform activities on our behalf, as well as other members of the Razer group.  
      
    (a) **To provide and manage products and services you have requested** to administer our services, including to carry out our obligations arising from any agreements entered into between you and us, or to notify you about changes to our services and products.  
      
    **Use justifications**: contract performance; consent, legitimate interests (to enable us to perform our obligations and provide our services to you or to notify you about changes to our service).  
      
    (b) **To sponsor you and/or your e-sports team** to carry out our obligations arising from any sponsorship agreements entered into between you and us, to notify you about changes to the terms of our sponsorship, or to advertise the fact that you and/or your e-sports team are sponsored by us.  
      
    **Use justifications**: contract performance; consent.  
      
    (c) **To communicate with you regarding products and services that may be of interest** to provide you with updates and offers, where you have chosen to receive these. We may also use your information to market our own and our selected business partners' products and services to you by way of in-app alerts, post, email, phone, SMS or online or social media advertisement. Where required by law, we will ask for your consent at the time we collect your data to conduct any of these types of marketing. We will provide an option on the appropriate platform to unsubscribe or opt-out of further communication on any electronic marketing communication sent to you.  
      
    **Use justifications**: legitimate interests (to keep you updated with news in relation to our products and services); consent.  
      
    (d) **To understand our customers and to develop and tailor our products and services** we may analyse the Personal Information we hold in order to better understand your usage patterns, preferences and marketing requirements, as well as to better understand our business and develop our products and services;  
      
    **Use justifications**: legitimate interests (to ensure the quality and legality of our services and to allow us to improve our services).  
      
    (e) **To monitor certain activities** to monitor queries and transactions to ensure service quality, compliance with procedures, terms of use and policies (including our Razer Insider House Rules), and to combat fraud (including running anti-fraud checks against your payment method when processing your order(s) on our website);  
      
    **Use justifications**: contract performance, legal obligations, legal claims, legitimate interests (to ensure that the quality and legality of our services).  
      
    (f) **To inform you of changes** to notify you about changes to our services and products.  
      
    **Use justifications:** legitimate interests (to notify you about changes to our service).  
      
    (g) **To ensure website content is relevant** to ensure that content from our websites is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device, which may include passing your data to business partners, suppliers and/or service providers.  
      
    **Use justifications:** legitimate interests (to allow us to provide you with the content and services on the websites).  
      
    (h) **To reorganize or make changes to our business** in the event that we: (i) are subject to negotiations for the sale of our business or part thereof to a third party; (ii) are sold to a third party; or (iii) undergo a re-organization, we may need to transfer some or all of your Personal Information to the relevant third party (or its advisors) as part of any due diligence process for the purpose of analyzing any proposed sale or re-organization. We may also need to transfer your Personal Information to that re-organized entity or third party after the sale or reorganization for them to use for the same purposes as set out in this policy.  
      
    **Use justifications:** legitimate interests (in order to allow us to change our business).  
      
    (i) **In connection with legal or regulatory obligations** We may process your Personal Information to comply with our regulatory requirements or dialogue with regulators as applicable which may include disclosing your Personal Information to third parties, the court service and/or regulators or law enforcement agencies in connection with enquiries, proceedings or investigations by such parties anywhere in the world or where compelled to do so. Where permitted, we will direct any such request to you or notify you before responding unless to do so would prejudice the prevention or detection of a crime.  
      
    **Use justifications:** legal obligations, legal claims, legitimate interests (to cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory authorities).  

4. **4\. Profiling and Automated Decision Making**  
    The advertisements and recommendations (including online, while you are logged into your Razer ID account, and while you are using our mobile app) which we show you are chosen by analysing the Personal Information you provide to us as described in section 2, including information about your past purchases from us, the way in which you use our products and/or services, and previous advertisements which you have clicked on. To choose advertisements which are tailored and most likely to be of interest to you, we compile and analyse information received from all our customers to gain a better understanding of your preferences from customers similar to you.  
      
    We use similar predictive techniques to combat payment fraud, as described below.  

5. **5\. Identity Verification**  
    When you create an account or initiate a transaction on our site, we may process your Personal Information (including your name, mobile number, identification number, passport number, nationality, address, date of birth and related documents including your identification card, passport, proof of residence documents such as utility, phone or bank statements and/or government agency letter) for the purposes of identity verification checks and/or to comply with our know-your-customer obligations under applicable laws. You may submit such Personal Information to us through a third party such as Jumio ([http://www.jumio.com](http://www.jumio.com/)) or SingPass MyInfo ([http://api.singpass.gov.sg/](http://api.singpass.gov.sg/)). If the Personal Information submitted to us is insufficient, inaccurate and/or does not pass our identity verification checks in our view, we may disable your account and/or decline to process your transaction(s). In the event you selected biometric verification as an authentication option, then Razer will collect and process a public key generated by your device for the purpose of (a) identity recognition; (b) login verification; and/or (c) transaction instruction verification. This public key is generated by your device using public key cryptography and sent to Razer when you select biometric verification. Upon receipt by Razer, this public key will be associated with your RazerID account, so that RazerID can recognize and verify your device. In doing so, Razer does not process or access any biometric information stored on your device, including your private key kept in your device. For avoidance of doubt, Razer does not collect, transfer, process, control or possess any biometric information that you may have stored on your device (eg. fingerprints, faceprints, and voiceprints, iris or retina scans, keystroke, gait, or other physical patterns, and sleep, health, exercise, genetic, physiological, behavioral or biological data).  

6. **6\. Processing of Payments on our Site**  
    When you submit a payment request on our site (including when making purchases from our online store, or when purchasing Razer Gold or Razer Silver), we pass your payment information (including information about your past transactions, the current transaction, your Razer ID, credit card details and IP address) to a third party service provider, namely Forter ([http://www.forter.com](http://www.forter.com/)) which conducts anti-fraud checks on our behalf. Our online store merely queries whether the payment information provided by you satisfies the criteria set by Forter's algorithm and then returns back the results. If your payment information does not satisfy Forter's criteria, the payment request will be declined.  
      
    This process may result in you not being able to complete a purchase on our site. You may want to check your payment information or try again using a different method of payment. Otherwise, you may request that we provide information about our decision-making methodology and ask us to verify that the automated decision has been made correctly. We may reject the request, as permitted by applicable law, including when providing the information would result in a disclosure of a trade secret or would interfere with the prevention or detection of fraud or other crime but generally in these circumstances we will ask Forter to verify that its algorithm and source data are functioning as anticipated without error or bias.  

7. **7\. Sharing your Personal Information (and transfers outside of the EEA)**  
    We will only use or disclose your Personal Information for the purpose(s) it was collected and as otherwise identified in this Privacy Policy.
    1. **Sharing outside the Razer group**: Personal Information may be provided to third parties, including anti-fraud organisations, legal, regulatory or law enforcement authorities in cases of suspected criminal activity or contravention of law, for the detection and prevention of fraud, or when required to satisfy the legal or regulatory requirements of governments, regulatory authorities or other self-regulatory organizations, or to comply with a court order or for the protection of our assets (for example, collection of overdue accounts).
    2. **Sharing within the Razer group**: We may share your Personal Information within the Razer group, including locations outside of the European Economic Area where we do business, for marketing purposes, for legal and regulatory purposes, to manage credit risk and other business risks, to perform analytics, to ensure we have correct or up to date information about you (such as your current address or date of birth) and to better manage your relationship with us.
    3. **Business sale or reorganization**: Over time, we may buy new businesses or sell some of our businesses. Accordingly, Personal Information associated with any accounts, products or services of the business being purchased or sold will be reviewed as part of the due diligence process and subsequently transferred as a business asset to the new business owner. We may also transfer Personal Information as part of a corporate reorganization or other change in corporate control.
    4. **Sub-contractors and agents**: We may use affiliates or other companies to provide services on our behalf such as data processing, account administration, fraud prevention and detection, analytics and marketing. Such companies will be given only the Personal Information needed to perform those services and we do not authorize them to use or disclose Personal Information for their own marketing or other purposes. We have contracts in place holding these companies to the same standards of confidentiality by which we are governed.  

8. **8\. EEA Rights to Personal Information / GDPR**  
    EEA individuals have the right, under certain circumstances, to:
    
    * Access their personal information;
    * Correct inaccurate personal information;
    * Request erasure of their personal information without undue delay;
    * Request the restricted processing of their personal information;
    * To receive the personal information that they have provided us with, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and you have the right to transmit that information to another controller without hindrance or ask us to do so; and
    * To object to the processing of their personal information.

    Such users may request access to their personal information and modify or remove most information associated with their Razer account at any time by logging into their Razer account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info. Users may also email to exercise any of the above rights by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.razer.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  
      
    EU users also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the EU Member State of their habitual residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement if they consider that our processing of their personal information infringes the applicable data protection laws. Please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.razer.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will provide you with detailed information regarding the contact details of the respective competent supervisory authority.  

9. **9\. Transfers Outside of the EEA**  
    Your Personal Information may be accessed by staff, suppliers or other persons in, transferred to, and/or stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (EEA) in which data protection laws may be of a lower standard than in the EEA. We will, in all circumstances, safeguard personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy.  
      
    Where we transfer Personal Information from inside the European Economic Area (the EEA) to outside the EEA, we may be required to take specific additional measures to safeguard the relevant Personal Information. Certain countries outside the EEA have been approved by the European Commission as providing essentially equivalent protections to EEA data protection laws and therefore no additional safeguards are required to export Personal Information to these jurisdictions. In countries which have not had these approvals (see the full list here [https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions\_en](https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions_en)), we will establish legal grounds justifying such transfer, such as EU Commission-approved model contractual clauses, or other legal grounds permitted by applicable legal requirements.  
      
    If you live outside the EEA, or California, Razer will undertake best efforts to give you a similar degree of control over your privacy.  

10. **10\. Security of your Personal Information**  
    (a) We use physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect against unauthorized use, access, modification, destruction, disclosure, loss or theft of your Personal Information in our custody or control.  
      
    (b) We have agreements and controls in place with third party service providers requiring that any information we provide to them must be safeguarded and used only for the purpose of providing the service we have requested the company to perform.  

11. **11\. Security over the Internet**  
    (a) No data transmission over the Internet or website can be guaranteed to be secure from intrusion. However, we maintain commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your Personal Information in accordance with data protection legislative requirements.  
      
    (b) All information you provide to us is stored on our or our subcontractors' secure servers and accessed and used subject to our security policies and standards. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our websites, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential and for complying with any other security procedures that we notify you of. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.  

12. **12\. Retention of your Personal Information**  
    Our retention periods for personal data are based on business needs and legal requirements. We retain your Personal Information for as long as is necessary for the processing purpose(s) for which the information was collected, and any other permissible, related purpose. For example, we may retain certain transaction details and correspondence until the time limit for claims arising from the transaction has expired, or to comply with regulatory requirements regarding the retention of such data. When Personal Information is no longer needed, we either irreversibly anonymise the data (and we may further retain and use the anonymised information) or securely destroy the data.  

13. **13\. Marketing**  
    Most of our processing is permitted by "legal grounds" other than consent (see section 2 above). In relation to Direct Marketing, where we are required to do so, we will obtain your consent before using your Personal Information for this purpose. If you prefer not to receive our Direct Marketing communications and/or not have your Personal Information shared among the members of the Razer group for the purpose of marketing, you can have your name deleted from our Direct Marketing and/or shared information lists.  
      
    Direct Marketing means our communication with you such as mail, telemarketing or email, using your contact information, to inform you about products and services that we think may be of interest and value to you. This does not include communications regarding products or services that you currently have, including improved ways to use the products, or additional features of the products as well as transactional information.  

14. **14\. Updating information**  
    We will use reasonable endeavours to ensure that your Personal Information is accurate. In order to assist us with this, you should notify us of any changes to the Personal Information that you have provided to us by contacting us as set out in the "Contacting Us" section below.  

15. **15\. Your rights**  
    If you have any questions in relation to our use of your Personal Information, you should first contact us as per the "Contacting Us" section below. Under certain conditions, you may have the right to require us to:  
      
    (a) provide you with further details on the use we make of your information;  
      
    (b) provide you with a copy of information that you have provided to us;  
      
    (c) update any inaccuracies in the Personal Information we hold;  
      
    (d) delete any Personal Information the we no longer have a lawful ground to use;  
      
    (e) where processing is based on consent, to withdraw your consent so that we stop that particular processing;  
      
    (f) object to any processing based on the legitimate interests ground unless our reasons for undertaking that processing outweigh any prejudice to your data protection rights;  
      
    (g) restrict how we use your information whilst a complaint is being investigated; and  
      
    (h) Your exercise of these rights is subject to certain exemptions to safeguard the public interest (e.g. the prevention or detection of crime) and our interests (e.g. the maintenance of legal privilege). If you exercise any of these rights we will check your entitlement and respond in most cases within a month.  

16. **16\. Contacting us**  
    If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices, the privacy of your Personal Information or you want to change your privacy preferences, please contact us through [this form](https://www.razer.com/privacy-enquiries). You can also directly contact our Data Protection Officer at [\[email protected\]](https://www.razer.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  

17. **17\. Cookies policy**  
    We use cookies on the websites. To find out more about how we use cookies, please see our Cookies Policy at [http://www.razer.com/legal](http://www.razer.com/legal).  

18. **18\. Changes to our Privacy Policy and/or Cookies Policy**  
    We may change the content of our websites and how we use cookies and consequently our Privacy Policy and our Cookie Policy may change from time to time in the future. If we change this Privacy Policy or our Cookies Policy, we will update the date it was last changed below. If these changes are material, we will indicate this clearly on our Website.

ANNEX  
PRIVACY STATEMENT- CALIFORNIA
-------------------------------------

1. **19\. Your California Privacy Rights**  
    In addition to the details about personal information we collect from consumers described above, this section provides the rights afforded to California consumers under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, as amended, including by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020, or collectively, the “CCPA.”  
      
    CCPA Rights Disclosure: If you are a California resident, the CCPA allows you to make certain choices regarding your personal information, as described below.  
      
    Access: You have the right to request, twice in a 12-month period, that we disclose to you the personal information we have collected, used, disclosed and sold about you during the past 12 months.  
      
    Data Portability: You have the right to receive a copy of your personal information we have collected from you by mail or electronically, including the right to request that we transmit specific personal information to another entity to the extent technically feasible, in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format.  
      
    Deletion: You have the right to request that we delete certain personal information we have collected from you.  
      
    Correct: You have the right to request that we correct any inaccurate personal information that you have provided us.  
      
    Opt-Out of Sale and Sharing: You have the right to opt-out of the sale and sharing of your personal information.  
      
    Limit Use and Disclosure: You have the right to limit the use and disclosure of your personal information to that only which is necessary for us to perform the services or provide the goods as requested from us.  
      
    Shine the Light Request: You also may have the right to request that we provide you with (a) a list of certain categories of personal information we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year and (b) the identity of those third parties.  
      
    The CCPA further provides you with the right to not be discriminated against (as provided for in applicable law) for exercising your rights. Please note that certain information may be exempt from such requests under California law. For example, we need to retain certain information in order to provide services to you. We also will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before responding to a request from you or an authorized agent. We do not use automated decision making technology nor do we sell the personal information of any California resident under the age of 16. If you would like further information regarding your legal rights under California law or would like to exercise any of them, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.razer.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  

2. **20\. Changes to Our Privacy Notice**  
    We reserve the right to amend this privacy notice at our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to this privacy notice, we will notify you by email or through a notice on our website homepage and update the notice’s effective date.

Shop

Explore

Support

Company

Follow Us

FOR GAMERS. BY GAMERS.™

Copyright © 2024 Razer Inc. All rights reserved.

United States

FOR GAMERS. BY GAMERS.™

Here’s $10 Off\* to Get You Started
===================================

Sign up for the Razer newsletter and enjoy $10 off your purchase.
-----------------------------------------------------------------

Enter your email address

Please enter a valid email address

By signing up, you agree to receive emails from Razer about products, news, events and promotions (including offers and discounts). For more details see our

SIGN UP NOW

\*Offer is valid with a minimum purchase of $99.

Thanks for signing up.

Check your inbox and verify your email address to receive your $10 off promo code.

Loading...
